人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  草草
翻譯  國士章魚X
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯  癢癢惦記小跟班
翻譯  江湖人稱王姑娘
翻譯  沫沫
時間軸  吉吉
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第十三集
我是總統
This is the president.
-讓康威接電話  -你要跟我說話
- Put on Conway. - You will speak to me.
不  我們只跟他談  否則掛斷
No, we only talk to him or we hang up.
聽到直升機了嗎  或是狗吠
Do you hear the helicopters yet? Or the dogs?
我們接近了  很快就能找到你們
We're getting closer and we will find you.
唯一的問題是  我們抓到你們之前
The only question is will you work with us
你們是否愿意合作
before we get there?
贖金和撤軍都別指望了
The money's not happening and neither is the military withdrawal.
但你夠聰明  早就知道
But you're smart enough to know that.
重點在于艾哈邁迪
The objective here is Ahmadi,
這是我想談的
and that's what I'd like to discuss.
選擇權在你
Well, the choice is yours.
你要么滿足我們的要求  要么不滿足
You either meet our demands or you don't.
我昨晚跟康威州長深談過
I spoke at length last night with Governor Conway.
我今早本想無視你的電話
I was of a mind to ignore your call this morning,
但他說服我繼續跟你溝通
but he convinced me that we should keep talking.
是吧  州長
Isn't that right, Governor?
-我只想尋求和平的解決方案  -我也是
- I just want a peaceful resolution. - As do I.
你想叫上州長  我想叫上艾哈邁迪
You wanted to include the Governor, I want to include Ahmadi.
-你是在拖延  -你不想跟你的領袖說話嗎
- You're trying to stall. - You refusing to speak to your leader?
他在線嗎
Is he on now?
你釋放米勒一家  我們就讓他跟你通話
You release the Millers, then we put him on.
不  你無權談條件
No, you don't get to dictate terms.
你表現出誠意  我們才會還以誠意
We show good will when you show good will.
我給你10秒鐘重新考慮
I'm giving you ten seconds to reconsider your position.
之后  我們就切斷電話
After that, we disconnect the call.
真主的旨意  我們會殺了他們
Insha'Allah. We'll kill them.
10秒鐘  現在開始
Ten seconds, starting now.
5秒鐘
Five seconds.
-結束通話  -一個人質
- End the call. - One hostage.
-三個  -一個
- All three. - One.
把女兒和母親交出來
Give us the daughter and the mother.
不  女孩我們要留下
No, we keep the girl.
你已經兩次打通了
You managed to get the president of the United States
美國總統的電話
on the phone not once, but twice.
你得釋放女兒和母親
You will release the daughter and the mother
否則我再也不會與你聯絡了
or you will never hear from me again,
而且你會失去與你領袖通話的機會
and you will lose your chance to speak to your leader.
馬上說
Tell me now.
他們掛線了  先生
They've disconnected, sir.
站住
Stop.
艾哈邁迪先生
Mr. Ahmadi.
你可以在樓上洗澡  衣柜里有干凈衣服
You can shower upstairs. There's fresh clothes in the closet.
只有參聯會主席和護送他的
The only people who know are the Chairman
海豹突擊隊隊員知道
and the SEALs who escorted him.
-通話線路安全嗎  -直通總統辦公室
- Do we have a secure line? - Direct to the Oval.
總統先生
Mr. President...
換了我絕不會同意把艾哈邁迪扯進來
I would have never condoned bringing Ahmadi into this.
幸好  我做決定的依據
Well, lucky for me, I'm not making decisions
不是你會同意什么
based on what you would or would not condone.
等著我告訴媒體你把話強加于我
Watch me tell the press you put words in my mouth.
隨意
Feel free.
但我覺得他們不太可能會相信你
I think they'll have a hard time believing you, though.
看看你的信息  你的手下肯定一直在給你發郵件
Check your messages. I'm sure your staff's been emailing you.
安排車送州長和他家人去機場
Arrange for a car to get the governor and his family to the airport.
回紐約一路順風
Have a safe trip back to New York.
情報委員會成員稱  康威撒謊
我叫人送來了午餐
I've had lunch brought in.
你肯定挺久沒吃過熱乎乎的飯菜了
I'm sure it's been quite a while since you've had a hot meal.
-我不會吃的  -你不餓嗎
- I won't be eating it. - Aren't you hungry?
我不想受刑的時候吐出來
I don't wanna get sick while I'm being tortured.
沒人會給你用刑  請坐吧
No one's getting tortured. Please, have a seat.
你想要我叫他們放了那家人  是嗎
You want me to tell these men to release the family, right?
否則  你就得做你必須做的了
If I don't, you'll do what you have to do.
如果我們是那個意思
Oh, if we had any intention of that,
你就不可能離開關塔那摩
you never would have left Guantanamo.
我也不會來這兒
Nor would I be here.
這是哪里
Where is here?
弗吉尼亞州  政府安全屋
Virginia, in a government safe house.
為什么你來
And why you?
出于尊敬  由于事情重大
Out of respect... for the gravity of this situation.
我覺得你是想羞辱我
I think your intention is to humiliate me.
我給你提供了衣服  食物
You've been properly clothed, offered food.
怎么羞辱你了
How are we humiliating you?
我坐在一個女人對面
I'm sitting across from a woman.
沒必要裝樣子了
There's no reason to keep up the facade.
你和你弟弟不是原教旨主義者
You and your brother are not fundamentalists,
也不是敘利亞人
nor are you Syrian.
那是中情局告訴你的嗎
This what the CIA's feeding you?
你是伊拉克人  你真名是阿瓦德
You're Iraqi. Your real name is Al Awad.
事實上  這上面說
Actually, it says that
你2000年加入了復興社會黨
you joined the Baath Party in 2000.
你2001年到2002年間是
You were the assistant to the
基建副部長的助理
undersecretary of infrastructure, 2001, 2002.
隨你怎么說
Say whatever you want.
我弟弟會否認  你休想說服除你之外的任何人
My brother will deny. You won't convince anyone but yourselves.
我們驅逐了復興社會黨
We expel the Baathists
你就從官僚變成了極端主義者
and you go from a bureaucrat to an extremist.
但你是個受過高等教育的人  尤瑟夫
But you're a well-educated man, Yusuf...
你才不在乎伊斯蘭或哈里發
and you don't care about Islam or the caliphate.
你只是在利用那個刺激士兵情緒
You're just using that to radicalize soldiers.
就像你利用民主和自由那樣
Just as you use democracy and freedom.
現在我們理解彼此了
So now we understand each other.
尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪仍被單獨監禁在關塔那摩監獄
Yusuf Al Ahmadi remains in solitary confinement in Guantanamo.
如果卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒獲釋
If Caroline and Melissa Miller are released,
我們將允許劫持者在監督下與其通話
we will allow supervised contact with the kidnappers.
馬克
Mark.
艾哈邁迪一向鼓勵這樣的恐怖行動
Ahmadi has consistently encouraged acts of terror like this one.
你為什么認為任何的對話
What makes you think that any sort of dialogue
能帶來和平的結果
will lead to a peaceful resolution?
要么就是完全不建立對話
Well, the alternative is no dialogue at all.
我們想用盡一切辦法
We don't wanna leave any stone unturned.
莎拉
Sara.
你可否就《華爾街電訊報》的文章
Will you comment on the Wall Street Telegraph article
指出康威州長可能干涉了
about Governor Conway's alleged interference
眾議院情報委員會做出評論
with the House Intelligence Committee?
它確認了我們早有懷疑的事
Well, it confirms what we suspected to be true,
但你想聽的應該是州長的評論  而非我的
but I think you want the governor's comment, not ours.
沃勒克議員在扭曲事實
Congressman Walleck is misrepresenting events.
-你是說他撒謊了  -我是說他所言不實
- You're saying he lied? - I'm saying he misrepresented.
我在情報委員會有多位朋友
I have a number of friends on the Intelligence Committee,
我是否偶爾跟他們談話  當然
and do I speak with them sometimes? Of course.
但這跟干涉不是一回事
But that's not the same as interfering.
那么你從未跟委員會成員
So you never discussed the Russia plan
談論過俄羅斯計劃
with anyone on the committee?
我們或許談論過
We may have discussed it,
但我又沒下達命令
but it's not as though I was issuing orders.
而且我得說  大家現在應該首要關注
And I have to say, everyone's primary focus right now
米勒一家  而非此事
needs to be on the Miller family, not this.
總統是否要求你離開白宮
Did the president ask you to leave the White House?
我們都認為我該做的已經做完
Uh, we agreed that I'd done my part,
其他要靠他了
and that the rest is up to him.
能跟我們談談昨晚你跟總統
Can you tell us about your conversation last night
關于艾哈邁迪的討論嗎
with the president, regarding Ahmadi?
先說到這兒吧  謝謝大家
That'll be all for now. Thank you so much.
問個問題  先生
Question, sir.
走吧
Let's go.
等等  莉莉的車座還沒弄好
Uh, hold on, I'm still fastening Lily's car seat.
-威爾  -別說了
- Will-- - Not a word.
我得說  將軍對你說
Well, I have to tell you, the general's apeshit
為自己服役感到羞恥暴跳如雷
over what you said about being ashamed of your service.
他可能會接受采訪
He may talk to the press.
沒想出如何恰當地回應這堆狗屁
Nobody does any press until we have a proper response
誰都不許接受采訪
to all this shit.
爸爸說了  "狗屁"   狗屁  狗屁
Daddy said "Shit." Shit, shit, shit!
住口
Stop it!
你得給我挖到沃勒克的把柄
You need to bring me something on Walleck.
我們得讓他信譽掃地
We need to discredit him.
-弄好了沒有  -你不用沖我們撒火
- Are you done yet? - You don't need to snap at us.
-好了沒有  -好了
- Are you done yet? - Yes.
快走  馬上
Let's go. Now.
那是如果他們獲釋
That's if they're released.
等我們了解了具體情況會把空白處補上
We'll fill in the blanks once we have details.
這是為最糟糕的情況準備的
This is if the worst happens.
耶茨寫的嗎
Yates wrote these?
不  我先寫了一篇
No, I... I took a stab at it first.
另外  湯姆·漢默施密特打來了
Also, Tom Hammerschmidt called.
他想采訪總統
He wants an interview with the president.
不肯說是什么事
He wouldn't say what for.
他現在是哪家的
What outlet is he with now?
他回《先驅報》了  說給你發了郵件
He's back at the Herald. Said he emailed you directly.
雷米·丹頓  杰姬·夏普和加勒特·沃克均已公開作證
讓我單獨待會兒
I need the room.
都出去
Everyone out.
接《先驅報》
Get me the Herald.
湯姆·漢默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
這里有個手機信號塔
Well, there's a cell tower here.
一般流量不多
Uh, typically very low traffic,
但在來電期間有增加
but it showed higher usage during the time of the call,
尤其是東南天線
especially the southeastern antenna.
那么我們應該能定位熱點  鎖定位置
So we should be able to ping the hotspot, zero in?
信號塔很多
Eh, it's hundreds of tower faces.
我能說出大致區域
I can give you the general area,
具體定位要更久
but pinpointing will take longer.
而且我無法保證肯定是他們
I can't even guarantee it's gonna be them.
分析每一座塔
I want every one of those towers analyzed.
專注分析背景環境聲音會更有收效
Well, we're better off concentrating on ambient background sound.
如果我能把那個跟這一帶
If I can match that to other calls made
同一時段內的其他通話匹配上
in this area around the same time as--
我不是在問你的建議
I'm not asking your advice.
我是告訴你該做什么
I'm telling you what I want you to do.
分析信號塔數據
Focus on the tower data.
我們本來關注的是這一帶
We were concentrating on this area,
但看來他們更接近這里
but it looks like they're closer to here.
我們安排了地面小隊展開了搜查網絡
We've got ground teams setting up a search grid.
可以用衛星嗎
Can we use satellites?
我們用了  但區域內有數百個
We are, but there are over 100 possible structures
可能建筑
within the zone.
-要逐個搜查  -要多久
- Each one of them needs to be checked. - How long?
如果走運  幾小時  要不可能拖到明天
If we get lucky, within hours. If not, could be tomorrow.
先生  斯坦普先生來了
Sir, Mr. Stamper's here.
-他說是急事  -謝謝
- He says it's urgent. - Thank you.
湯姆·漢默施密特說他們今天就會發布
Hammerschmidt says they go online today,
不管您是否做出評價
whether you comment or not.
出行記錄不算鐵證
Travel logs are not hard evidence.
這些引言都是間接證據
These quotes are circumstantial.
但加在一起  我不知道我們該怎么解釋
But all of it combined... I don't know how we spin this.
有分量很重的人愿公開作證
He's got heavy hitters on the record.
要我放出杰姬和雷米的照片嗎
Should I release the photos of Jackie and Remy?
他們把外遇的事告訴他了
They told him about the affair.
他要在文章里寫我們曾威脅曝光他們
He's putting in the article that we threatened to expose them.
怎么會發生這種事
How did this happen?
你也有責任
This is as much on you.
我可以列出一張他還沒找到的人的名單
I can put together a list of the people he hasn't gotten to yet.
讓他拿到掩蓋的證據嗎
And give him proof of a cover-up?
他說得對  如果我們再聯絡塔斯克或拉尼根
He's right. If we reach out to Tusk or Lanagin--
把漢默施密特叫來
I want Hammerschmidt here.
-先生  我不是說...  -盡快安排
- Sir, I wasn't suggesting-- - Set it up as soon as possible.
美國政府絕不會承認哈里發
The U.S. Government will never recognize the caliphate.
當然
No, of course not.
但我們能讓復興社會黨重回政府
But we can reintegrate the Baathists into the government.
什么政府  伊拉克已經沒有政府了
What government? There's no government in Iraq.
伊拉克已經沒有了  有巴格達
There is no Iraq. There's Baghdad.
什葉派  遜尼派  庫爾德派
Shia, Sunni, Kurd...
敘利亞也是如此
Syria is the same.
我們驅逐你們之前  你們維持了秩序
You maintained order before we shut you out.
我們不能支持神政
Now, we can't support a theocracy,
但我們可以讓軍隊重新掌權
but we can put the military back in control.
我們招募的士兵怎么辦
What do we do with all the soldiers we've recruited?
他們不會接受世俗國家
They won't accept a secular government.
你要管好他們
You'll keep them in check.
如果有必要  靠武力
With force, if necessary.
沖替我們扛槍的人開槍嗎
Use our guns on the men who carried it for us.
那又如何  如果你能重新掌權的話
What does it matter... if you have back your power?
如果你們真這么打算  為什么不公開說
If this is your intention, why have you said nothing publicly?
因為你知道這一切
Because you know that all of this
只能閉門商量
has to be done behind closed doors.
我們得表現得像是我們消滅了哈里發國
We need to give the appearance that we neutralized ICO.
如果他們不釋放人質呢
What happens if they don't release the hostages?
那你回古巴
Well, then you go back to Cuba.
如果他們放了人質  我們就讓你跟他們通話
If they do, then we put you on the phone with them...
你叫他們把第三名人質也放掉
and you tell them to release the third.
然后你還是會送我回古巴
And then you send me back to Cuba anyway.
我明白你為什么不信任我們
I do understand why you don't trust us,
但另一個選擇呢
but what is the alternative?
他們死了  我們就更有理由
These people die, and then it gives us all the justification we need
全面進攻
for a full offensive.
那得要很多年
That's years...
而且你休想完全消滅我們
and you won't completely destroy us.
不能完全  但也足以讓你們不值一提
Not completely, but enough to make you irrelevant.
我們也可以悄悄合作
Or we can quietly work together.
哈里發國消亡  你和你的將軍們得到大權
ICO fades, and you and your generals get control.
-知道克萊爾在哪嗎  -不  我們在找她呢
- Do you know where Claire is? - No, we're trying to find her.
她如果要去哪一般會告訴我
She usually keeps me informed if she's going somewhere.
你問過特勤局嗎
Have you asked Secret Service?
-他們不知道  -他們肯定知道
- They didn't know. - They have to know.
我再去問問
I'll go ask again.
謝謝
Thanks.
她不在宅邸
She wasn't at the residence.
-你還去了那兒  -十分鐘前
- You went up there? - Ten minutes ago.
你倆到底怎么回事
What's going on between you two?
你以為我沒發現嗎
You think I haven't noticed?
你倆說話的樣子  你來得多勤
How you two talk? How often you're here?
我都不能隨隨便便進出宅邸
I don't even have unrestricted access to the residence.
她母親死時  我陪在她身邊
I was with her when her mother died.
這讓我們變得親近
It made us close.
你不要想太多
Don't read too much into it.
不管你們有多親近
Well, however close you are,
只要別讓外人想太多就好
just make sure that nobody else can read too much into it.
等你見到克萊爾  告訴她我回家了
Well, if you see Claire, tell her I went home.
如果她想找我的話
If she needs me.
不要和他面談
Don't meet face-to-face.
讓他以書面形式把問題傳給你
Have him submit the questions in writing.
但如果我見他  也許能讓他先停停
Yeah, but if I meet with him, maybe I can give him pause.
不  他是想誆你露出馬腳
No, he's trying to trap you into giving something away.
那絕不可能
That's not going to happen.
-真是挑了個好時候  -你那邊如何
- The timing on this-- - How's your end?
就要說通他了
He's getting there.
你集中精力對付他  我對付哈默施密特
Well, you focus on him. I'll handle Hammerschmidt.
你在抽煙嗎
Are you smoking?
-你怎么知道  -我能聽見
- How did you know? - I can hear it.
如果這報道出來
If this story comes out,
害死我們的不會是煙
it won't be the smoking that does us in.
他們被殺了嗎
Have they been killed?
你好像不高興
You look upset.
你想你妻子嗎
Do you miss your wife?
你才不在乎我妻子
You don't care about my wife.
你們夫妻倆我都不在乎
Ah, I don't care about either of you...
你們或是你們的孩子是死是活  我都不在乎
whether you live or die... or your children do.
但如果每月讓你和家人通一次話能說通你
But if speaking to your family once a month will get us there,
我會考慮的
I'll put that on the table.
我已經三年沒見過我妻子了
I haven't seen my wife in three years.
我從來沒見過我兒子  我女兒根本不記得我
I have a son I've never met, a daughter that doesn't remember me.
這是我們選擇的路
This is our path.
哪怕他們被殺嗎
Even if they're killed?
是的
Yes.
他們會被殺的
Because they will be.
我不惜一死  他們也是一樣
I'm willing to die, and so are they.
-這是他們的選擇嗎  -什么選擇
- Would they have made that choice? - What choice?
他們只知道你們的炸彈
All they've known are your bombs.
一彈下來  人沒了
Poof, gone.
我們的厲害之處
We're effective
就在于我們讓你們感受到了那痛苦
because we make you feel the pain.
而我們一生都在承受這種痛苦
We've felt it all our lives.
進
Yes?
-湯姆  -總統先生
- Tom. - Mr. President.
我得說明白  今天我們的談話不能公開
I'm gonna ask that everything we discuss today is off the record.
-明白  -上次我們見面的時候
- Understood. - Now, the last time we met,
是在副總統辦公室
it was in the vice president's office,
你指控我靠操縱馬修斯當上了副總統
and you claim that I acquired that office by manipulating Matthews.
指控你的不是我  是沃克總統
I don't claim that. President Walker does.
是啊  那個自食苦果心懷怨憤的男人
Oh, yes. A man made bitter by his own mistakes.
你還聲稱  我靠陰謀趕走了他
And you also claim that I then acquired this office
才坐上了總統之位
by pushing out that very same man.
-丹頓和夏普證實了此事  -是嗎
- Danton and Sharp corroborated. - Oh, yes.
這兩個人和我有很深的宿怨
Two people with very big chips on their shoulders,
無非是想給他們的出軌編個借口罷了
fabricating all this nonsense to justify their infidelity.
你是說你沒脅迫過他們
You're saying you didn't blackmail them?
我曾對許多人施壓  湯姆
I pressure a lot of people, Tom.
這是政治的一部分
That's part of politics.
但從沒威脅過他們
But never those two.
丹頓的父母說
Danton's parents say
莉安·哈維去過他們在邁阿密的家
LeAnn Harvey came to their house in Miami.
那應該是他想拉攏莉安支持他的俄羅斯計劃
Well, I imagine that's because he wanted LeAnn on the Russian plan.
那為什么是她上門  而不是他去找她
Then why did she come to him instead of him coming to her?
我不想跟你糾結這些細枝末節
Look, I'm not gonna get into the weeds on this,
我們還是直說了吧
but let's just cut to the chase.
你現在提出的這些指控
The allegations that you're making
就和你第一次見我時所說的一樣都是胡扯
are just as ludicrous as they were the first time we met.
我當時沒什么確鑿證據  這回我有了
I had nothing concrete then. This time I do.
就光那三個急于報復我的人
Three people with an ax to grind,
出行記錄  連點干貨都沒有嗎
no hard evidence and some travel logs?
這算什么"確鑿"證據
I'd hardly call that concrete.
寫報道已經夠了
It's enough for a story.
你這簡直是憑空捏造
You're floating an idea out of thin air.
讓我戳穿你的真實意圖吧  你就是想趁大選
Let's just call this what it is: blatant sensationalism
-搞個大新聞嘩眾取寵  -我沒有捏造
- tied to the election-- - I don't float.
...嘩眾取寵來提升你們的發行量
tied to an election to boost your circulation
因為《先驅報》的讀者在大量流失
because the Herald is losing readership.
先生  我決不會捏造故事試探風向
Sir, I don't float stories to see if they're seaworthy,
我對發行量更是毫不在乎
and I don't give a shit about circulation.
我現在只關心真相
The only thing I care about is the truth.
真相  那你聯系雷蒙德·塔斯克
The truth? So have you reached out to Raymond Tusk
要他評論了嗎  或是丹尼爾·拉尼根
for a comment? Or Daniel Lanagin?
我可沒看見他們的引述
I don't see their quotes in here.
如果你真的要查真相
I mean, if you're going for the truth,
難道不該查得全面一點  公正一點嗎
doesn't that include being thorough? Being balanced?
所以我才想給你機會就此事發表評論
Which is why I'm giving you an opportunity to comment.
那有沒有國會議員
And what about any members of Congress?
我也沒看見他們的話
I don't see their quotes in here.
相信等文章發布  他們會接我的電話的
I'm sure they'll answer my calls once this article comes out.
我看你壓根不敢打給他們
Oh, I think you're afraid to make those calls,
因為你知道他們會看穿報道的實質
'cause you know they'll see this for what it is...
全無根據的小報八卦
unsupported tabloid gossip.
助理黨鞭  你的前幕僚長
The assistant whip, your former Chief of Staff,
外加一位美國前總統
an ex-president of the United States.
這可不是八卦  這是新聞
That's not gossip. It's news.
司法部肯定會展開聽證調查的
There's no way the Justice Department doesn't open up an inquiry.
就算司法部無視  國會的共和黨也不會放過
And if they don't, the Republicans in Congress will.
隨你貶低我  但你知道這事會是什么結果
Downplay this all you want, but you know where this story leads.
我知道這是怎么回事
I know what this story is.
政治陷害  就這么簡單
Political sabotage, plain and simple.
瑪格麗特·蒂爾頓以前可沒這么下作  湯姆
Margaret Tilden used to have some integrity, Tom.
你也是
And so did you.
你為什么要浪費全國人民的時間
Why are you wasting America's time with this,
非挑眼下這個危急關頭
in the middle of this crisis?
你的良心哪去了
Where is your conscience?
我也想問你這個問題
That's the question I want you to answer.
什么事
Yes?
先生  他們把母女倆的地址發過來了
Sir, they emailed a location of the mother and daughter.
麻煩把漢默施密特先生帶去羅斯福室
Will you please show Mr. Hammerschmidt into the Roosevelt Room?
不用了  我這就走
There's no need. I'll be going.
那可不行  咱倆話還沒說完呢  湯姆
Oh, no, no, no. You and I are not done, Tom.
卡洛琳和梅莉沙·米勒已于
Caroline and Melissa Miller were rescued
東部時間12:30左右被聯調局外勤探員解救
at approximately 12:30 Eastern Standard Time by FBI field agents.
除了綁架造成的精神創傷之外
Aside from the psychological trauma of their ordeal,
兩人健康狀況良好
both are unharmed and healthy.
我馬上會聯系她們  她們接受體檢后
I'll be calling them soon, and I hope to meet them soon,
我希望能盡快見到她們
once they have had their full medical examinations.
卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒獲救
雖然我對母女二人平安感到寬慰
And while I am greatly relieved to have them both safe,
但詹姆斯·米勒仍處境危險
James Miller remains in danger.
我們將拼盡全力  爭取我能再在這個講臺上
And we will not rest until I can come to this podium
發布這樣的好消息
and make another announcement like this one,
向各位通報他的平安
informing you of his safe return.
格雷森先生將繼續回答各位的問題
Mr. Grayson will answer any questions you may have.
我得回去主持營救了  謝謝各位
I must get back to work. Thank you all very much.
他們還活著  多少有你點功勞
They're alive. You can take some credit for that.
安德伍德肯定正把她們接去白宮
I'm sure Underwood's flying them to the White House right now.
人人都會記住這個鏡頭
That's the image everyone will remember.
熱烈的擁抱  安撫的話語
The warm embrace, the reassuring words.
他一點功勞都不會分給我的
I mean, he's not gonna let me take one ounce of credit for this.
詹姆斯·米勒搜救工作仍在進行
如果她們愿意見媒體的話
If they choose to talk with the media, however,
我們肯定會進行安排
we will certainly facilitate that.
現在請各位提問
I will now take some of your questions.
如果我和莉莉被綁了呢
What if it were Lily and me?
威爾  如果是我和莉莉被綁架了呢
Will, what if it were me and Lily?
你也會這么考慮嗎
Would this be your thinking?
-"政治影響"  -別  漢娜
- "The political fallout"? - Don't, Hannah.
別突然變軟弱了
Don't get weak on me.
我可以確認我們的重點搜索區域在那里
I can confirm that that is an area where our focus is,
但我只能說到這一步了
but that's about as much detail as I can go into.
綁匪和你們聯系了嗎
Have the kidnappers made contact?
如果聯系了
And if so,
你們讓他們和艾哈邁迪對話了嗎
did you put them in touch with Ahmadi?
他們尚未聯系我們  我們敦促他們盡快聯系
They have not made contact. We encourage them to do so.
而且我方的提議仍然有效
And, yes, the offer still stands.
-瑪麗  -你們憑什么確信
- Mary. - Uh, what assurances do you have
艾哈邁迪會照你們的意思進行對話
that Ahmadi will say what you want him to?
我們不能確信  也不能強迫他
We don't, and we can't force him to.
但我們希望他能和我們合作
But we're hoping that he will work with us on this.
古巴那邊是誰負責監督他進行通話
Who's managing the call from his side in Cuba?
抱歉  我不能透露
I'm sorry, I can't go into details on that.
雖然母女倆都被蒙了眼
Both were blindfolded in the car,
但母親估計他們開了45分鐘的車
but the mother estimates a drive time of 45 minutes.
這就使搜索范圍縮小到六棟建筑
That narrows the search to six structures.
也許他們已經逃跑了
Unless they're on the move.
即便他們穿過了路障
If they're past the roadblocks already,
那也得停下來打電話
they've gotta stop somewhere to make the call.
我們追蹤電話取得了進展
And we've had some progress on tracing the call.
你們把我的算法都拿去了
You're taking my algorithms.
我們需要更多人手  而這里又坐不下
We need more teams on this. There is not enough room here.
你知道我接到命令是
You know my instructions were
任何東西都不能離開這棟樓
never to let anything leave this building.
而我們有局長的直接命令
We have an order from the director.
如果你們讓更多人攙和進來會造成混亂的
Well, if you put more teams on this, it'll cause confusion.
回家吧  麥卡倫先生  你在這兒熬兩天了
Go home, Mr. Macallan. You've been here for two days straight.
我決不會把這事交給
I am not leaving this in the hands of people
不清楚情況的人
who do not know what they're doing.
我們能行
We've got it covered.
回家休息吧  需要的話會聯系你的
Go home. Get some rest. We'll let you know if we need you.
這兩個小子并不想殺人
These boys don't wanna kill anyone.
否則  就不會釋放兩名人質
If they did, they wouldn't have released two hostages.
他們其實是在找臺階下
They're actually looking for an excuse to back out.
如果對話視頻上了電視  我就成了叛徒
If the media plays that video, I look like a traitor.
我們告訴他們這是前提條件
We tell them it's a precondition.
要是他們敢泄露  協議就取消
If they share it, the deal is off.
我怎么知道你不會泄露呢
How do I know you won't?
我不能逼你相信我
I can't force you to believe me...
但我們只需幾小時就能找到他們
but we are hours from finding them.
你知道規矩
And you know how this goes.
要是吉姆·米勒死了  他們也會死
Jim Miller dies. They die.
你回古巴  我們開戰
You go back to Cuba. We go to war.
我們已經在交戰了
We're already at war.
尤瑟夫  你有一次
Yusuf, you have one chance
改變家鄉情況的機會
to change the conditions at home.
你浪費機會  就毀了你為之奮斗過的一切
You squander it, you destroy everything you have ever fought for.
你知道奮斗的滋味嗎
What do you know about fighting for anything?
我們說完了  把他押回去
We're done here. Send him back.
好吧
All right.
我照你說的做
I'll do what you ask.
給他穿上囚服  我們在地下室拍
Put him back in his jumpsuit. We'll film in the basement.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
告訴參議員  我回來就給他打電話
Tell the senator I'll call him when I get back.
-總統先生  -凱茜
- Mr. President. -Oh, Cathy.
我知道我們都沒機會討論這一切
I realize we haven't had a chance to discuss everything.
等到把人質救出來
We'll talk foreign policy consequences
我們就討論外交政策的后果
once we've resolved this hostage situation.
不是那事  《先驅報》聯系我了
It's not that. The Herald contacted me.
一名記者打到我辦公室  我讀過郵件了
A reporter called my office. I've read the email.
-你沒給他們回電  -當然沒
- You didn't call them back? - 'Course not.
好  什么都別做也別說  我來處理
All right. Don't do or say anything. I'll handle it.
-怎么處理  -我還不知道
- How? - I don't know yet.
沃克說我們同謀拿下了國務卿之位
Walker says we conspired for Secretary of State,
還說我在調查中庇護他
and saying I gave him asylum during the investigation.
要是他們發布這些  我也會被活剝
If they publish this, I get skinned alive, too.
我們會沒事的  凱茜  相信我
We're going to be all right, Cathy. Trust me on this.
我剛和國務卿杜蘭特談過
I just spoke with Secretary Durant.
我們定好了時間
We have a timeline.
同事們要是沒我的消息
My folks don't hear from me,
就開始在整點打電話
they start making calls on the hour.
先打給杜蘭特
Durant was first.
再打給博奇
Birch is next.
然后是烏麥克
Then Womack.
接著是邁克爾·科恩
Michael Kern.
佐伊的文章毀了他的機會
It was Zoe's article that ruined his chances.
你認識她  你去過她家附近
You knew her. You were in her neighborhood.
這不負責任  湯姆
This is irresponsible, Tom.
整個國家正受到恐怖主義的重大威脅
When the whole nation is in the middle of this major terror threat.
獨裁者們也是這套邏輯
That's the same reasoning dictators use.
你讓我想到凱特·鮑德溫
You remind me a little bit of Kate Baldwin.
你失去了客觀性
You've lost your objectivity.
你竟然提到她  真是有趣
Uh, it's funny you mention her.
凱特認為盧卡斯有所發現  我讓她別管
Kate thought Lucas was onto something. I told her to let it go,
因為什么都沒有  但其實有
that there wasn't anything there, but there was.
那事實在哪  事實  不是引言  事實
Well, where are the facts? Facts, not quotes. Facts.
你想看事實
You wanna see a fact?
這就是事實
This is a fact.
我告訴你他瘋了  這就是證據
I told you he was crazy, and there's the proof.
他把事實搞錯了  但他的方向是對的
He had the facts wrong, but he had the story right.
他看透了你
He saw through you.
什么方向  我是個心理變態
So what is the story? That I'm some sort of psychopath?
我是個殺人犯
That I'm a killer?
我從不相信你是個殺人犯  現在也不信
Oh, I never believed you were a murderer, and I still don't.
但我越來越難以不去考慮這種可能性
But it's becoming harder not to entertain the thought.
那我要不要給你把槍  好讓你也來射殺我
Well, should I get you a gun, so you can shoot me, too?
他說中了你的靈魂
He was right about your soul.
說中了你骨子里的東西
What's in your bones.
你殘酷無情  腐化不堪
That you're ruthless. You're corrupt.
阻攔你的東西  你一律摧毀
You destroy whatever's in your path.
有哪個總統不符合你這番描述
Name me a president you wouldn't describe in exactly the same way.
我們都殘酷無情  都摧毀事物
We're all ruthless. We all destroy.
至于腐敗  那就是視角問題了
But corruption? That's a matter of perspective.
不
No.
是法律問題
It's a matter of law.
行了  你現在有點亂  湯姆
All right, you seem a little confused here, Tom.
上一秒還在談我的靈魂
One moment you're talking about my soul,
下一秒就跳到法律
and the next moment you want to get legal.
我們今天至少說明白點什么  好嗎
Let's at least achieve some clarity here today, shall we?
你想要事實真相嗎
You want the real story?
佐伊·巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes?
對  我們在工作上有交集
Yes, we knew each other. Professionally.
我們互相幫忙
I scratched her back and she scratched mine.
是你把這些印出來的
And you printed all of it.
你是她教育法案時的線人
You were her source for the education bill.
-還有邁克爾·科恩  -你拆他臺
- And Michael Kern. - You sabotaged him.
問問你自己  我為什么要做那些事
Okay, ask yourself why I would have done all those things.
因為那個教育法案太糟糕了
Because the education bill was a disaster,
我必須得幫總統跳出泥潭
and I had to move the president off of it.
因為邁克爾·科恩是個糟糕的國務卿人選
Because Michael Kern was a terrible choice for Secretary of State.
我們應該選個更好的  也確實選出來了  凱茜
We could do better, and we did, with Cathy.
我是在幫沃克
I was trying to help Walker.
我是在引導一位軟弱的總統走上正途
I was trying to steer a weak president in the right direction.
你要是想發表這些  盡管發表好了
Now, you want to print that story, you go right ahead.
但是其余的部分都是胡扯
But the rest of it is just nonsense.
你沒和雷蒙德·塔斯克達成任何協議
You didn't make any deals with Raymond Tusk?
-絕對沒有  -那你為什么赦免他
- Absolutely not. - Then why did you pardon him?
和我赦免了沃克是一個原因
Same reason I pardoned Walker.
因為這個國家必須向前看
Because the country had to move on.
彈劾的事不是你策劃的
You didn't orchestrate his impeachment?
我為什么會想彈劾一位
Why would I want to impeach a president
我拼命輔佐的總統呢
I was working so hard to help?
你還在這兒  他卻不在了
You're still here. He's not.
我曾盡力阻止他毀掉自己
I was trying to save him from himself.
很不幸  我失敗了
Unfortunately, I failed.
-你相信自己的直覺嗎  湯姆  -一直都信
- Do you trust your instincts, Tom? - I always have.
那你看著我的眼睛
Then look me in the eye.
我告訴你的是真相
I've told you the truth.
你說的話
What you said...
算公開聲明嗎
is it on the record now?
你相信我嗎
Do you believe me?
一點都不信
Not for a second.
那就不算  一個字都不算
Then, no. Not a word.
我們會給你幾個小時準備正式回應
We'll give you a few hours if you want to make an official comment.
我可以走了
I'm ready to go now.
如果他們放了那位父親  你就是個英雄
If they release the father, you're a hero.
還不夠  我不知道我們該怎么處理這篇報道
It's not enough. I don't know how we survive this story.
我腦子在不停地轉  一遍遍翻來覆去地想
My mind keeps racing, over and over and over again.
本可以處理得更好的事
What we could've done differently.
本可以掩蓋的線索
How we could've covered our tracks.
本應搞好的關系
The people we should've kept closer...
我害怕  克萊爾
I'm frightened, Claire.
如果我們不能防止損失
If we can't stop the damage,
就必須止損  弗蘭西斯
we have to control it, Francis.
辦法是有的  總是有的
There is a solution. There always is.
稍等
Hold on.
他們打來了  先生
They're on, sir.
我們剛收到消息
We just got word.
-他們打來了  -是的  我也剛剛得知
- They've called in. - Yes, I was just told.
好吧  先處理這件事  一件一件來吧
All right, this first. One thing at a time.
-連好了嗎  -是的  夫人
- The link is up? - Yes, ma'am.
我們已經找到了那棟建筑
We've located the building.
符合卡洛琳·米勒的描述
Matches the description from Caroline Miller
也符合到她們釋放地點的駕車時間
and the drive time from where they were found.
我們確定他們在那兒嗎
Are we certain that they're there?
不  先生  但我們有一隊人馬在趕去了
No, sir, but we have a team en route.
看看一會兒的通話情況如何
Let's see how the phone call goes,
然后我們再決定是否行動
and then we'll decide if we're gonna move.
開始連線了
The line is open.
接通吧
Go ahead.
-我是總統  -艾哈邁迪呢
- This is the president. - Where's Ahmadi?
一會兒就讓他視頻連線
We're about to connect him via video,
這樣你就知道他可以自由發言
so you know that he's speaking freely.
但是連線之前  記住
But before we do, be aware
如果你們把這段通話泄露給媒體
that if you release any of this call to the media,
我們討論過的所有提議都會作廢
anything we discuss will be off the table.
接通他
Put him on.
真主保佑
Assalam-alaikum.
真主也保佑你
Walaikum-assalam.
我知道你們在試圖營救我
I know you are trying to free me.
說英語
English.
聽我說
Listen to me.
你們已經完成了使命
You've already done your duty.
你們已經引起了世界的注意
You have made the world pay attention.
但是美國政府不會釋放我的
But the U.S. Government, they will not free me.
如果你們傷害了這個人
And if you harm this man,
他們會讓穆斯林流更多的血
they'll bring more bloodshed on Muslims.
放了他吧
Let him go.
他們向我保證只以綁架罪起訴你們
They have promised me they will only charge you for kidnapping...
而不是恐怖襲擊
not as terrorists.
你是受迫這么說的嗎
Are they forcing you to say this?
不是
No.
你在看誰
Who are you looking to?
關掉
Off.
他們掛了
They've hung up.
他剛剛說了什么
What did he just say?
你剛才說了什么
What did you say?
告訴我你說了什么
Tell me what you said.
我不是個叛徒
I'm not a traitor.
把他關在這兒
Keep him down here.
"把視頻發布出去
"Release the video.
艾哈邁迪與劫持者對話公布
如果他們不放我回家  就殺了他們
If they don't send me home, kill them.
如果他們找到你  殺了他
If they find you, kill him.
確保你有證據..."  然后就斷了
Make sure you have proof that I--" And then it goes black.
現在情況如何  我們并不清楚
Where that leaves us, we don't know right now.
白宮沒有向媒體通報  也沒有發布聲明
The White House has not briefed the press or issued any statement--
我該怎么說
What do I say to this?
-我們什么都不說  -不能不回應
- We say nothing. - No, I can't say nothing,
外面有100多個記者準備破門而入
'cause I got 100 reporters that are about to break down that door.
在了解確切情況前
We are not going to expose ourselves
我們不能暴露自己
until we have something concrete to go on.
等那男的人頭落地  還是到時也不說
Like the guy's head rolling? Or are you saying nothing then, too?
《先驅報》那篇文章呢
Or how about the Herald article?
等那發布了  你也準備什么都不說嗎
When that comes out, are you gonna say nothing?
賽斯...
Seth...
我可以把自己鎖在這個房間里
Look, I will lock myself up in here.
找個地縫鉆進去
I'll bury my head in the sand.
但最終  面對那群人的還是我
But eventually, it's me that has to face these people.
-我不能像你一樣藏起來  -閉嘴
- All right, I can't hide the way that you-- - Stop.
閉嘴
Stop!
控制好你自己
Keep your shit together.
行嗎
Okay?
吃點東西  閉閉眼歇會兒
Eat some food. Rest your eyes for a little bit.
等我有進一步消息了聯系你
I'll let you know when I know more.
-先生...  -現在不行
- Oh, sir, a-- - Not now.
-你把他帶到這兒來了  -我自己來的
- You brought him here? - I brought myself.
事情很嚴重  道格
It's serious, Doug.
就緒
Ready.
上  上  上
Go, go, go!
上  上  上  上
Go, go, go, go!
上  上  上
Go! Go! Go!
-安全  -安全
- Clear. - Clear.
安全
Clear.
-屋子是空的  -周圍安全
- It's empty. - All clear.
-是空的  先生  -已確認周圍安全
- It's empty, sir. - Confirmed. All clear.
-弗蘭西斯他們找到了...  -沒有
- -Francis, did they find-- - No.
我以為艾哈邁迪會...
I thought Ahmadi was going to...
已經到這一步了
No, we are where we are.
我們知道他是個風險
We knew it was a risk.
-你還好嗎  -我沒事
- You okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
我扶你上樓
Let's get you upstairs.
安德伍德踏入總統辦公室的歪門邪道
...15分鐘前由湯姆·漢默施密特發表
...by Tom Hammerschmidt, 15 minutes ago.
文中提到曾請總統做出評論
In the article, it says the President was asked to comment,
但遭到拒絕
but declined.
文中引用了包括前總統加勒特·沃克
Among those quoted are ex-President Garrett Walker,
眾議員杰姬...
Congresswoman Jackie--
你到現在接到了多少電話
How many phone calls have you got so far?
至少30個
Uh, at least 30.
-你呢  -我已經懶得數了
- You? - Ah, I stopped counting.
我們該去哪
Where should we go?
給我個驚喜吧
Surprise me.
不  我們什么都不說
No, we don't say anything.
讓他在聚光燈下燒幾天
We'll let him burn in the lights for a few days
看看情況如何
and see how this plays out.
然后在每個搖擺州放廣告
And then we blanket every swing state with ads.
30秒  沒聲音  只放標題
Thirty seconds, in silence. Just the headline.
讓它沉入人們的腦子里
Let that sink into people's gray matter.
好的  回頭聊
Okay. We'll talk soon.
過來  我想給你看個東西
Come here. I wanna show you something.
我還在生氣
I'm still upset.
你不能假裝什么都沒發生過
You can't pretend that nothing's happened.
我不軟弱
I am not weak.
我不該那么說  我知道你不
I shouldn't have said that. I know you're not.
我還知道點別的
And here's something else I know.
你就要成為下一位美國第一夫人了
You're gonna be the next First Lady of the United States.
好的  待在辦公室
All right, stay in your office.
我待會兒打給你
I'll call you back in a bit.
來點降壓藥和阿司匹林吧
Some Prinivil and aspirin, please.
已經發布了
It's out?
對
Yes.
麥卡倫找到了道格那兒
Doug's got Macallan with him, too.
他們在擴大他的項目  但不由他負責
They're expanding his program, but without him in charge.
那么我們在那頭也不安全
So we're not safe there, either.
如果他...
Well, if he was...
如果是他掌管還好  但不是  所以
if he was there to manage it, but he's not, so...
不  我們不安全
No, we're not safe.
-要我叫薩克遜醫生嗎  -不必
- Should I call Dr. Saxon? - No, it's not necessary.
-非常感謝  先這樣吧  -好的  先生
- Thank you very much. That'll be all. - Yes, sir.
還有三周...
Three weeks...
就要大選了
then the election.
毫無勝算
It's nothing.
然后我們敗選
And then we lose.
然后他們調查
And they investigate.
我們的一切...
And everything we...
都毀了
gone.
我覺得
I feel...
麻木
numb.
我也是
I do, too.
我們可以制造時間
We make time.
我們無法把一切逐個擊退  弗蘭西斯
We can't fight everything off one by one, Francis.
但如果我們讓這件事
But if we make this...
為我們所用
we make it work for us.
制造混亂
Create chaos.
不只是混亂
More than chaos.
戰爭
War.
恐懼
Fear.
殘忍
Brutal.
徹底
Total.
我受夠了試圖贏取人心
I'm done trying to win over people's hearts.
我們來攻擊人心吧
Let's attack their hearts.
我們可以利用恐懼
We can work with fear.
是的  沒錯
Yes, we can.
你應該換一套西裝
You should put on a fresh suit.
海軍藍
The navy blue.
對  就那件
Yes, the navy blue.
-麥卡倫呢  -我們讓他回去了
- Where's Macallan? - We sent him home.
好  讓他稍安勿躁  我們回頭處理
All right, tell him to stay put. We'll tackle that later.
讓賽斯聯系媒體  一小時后  總統辦公室
Have Seth inform the networks. The Oval, one hour.
-需要他起草什么嗎  -讓湯姆來寫
- Do you need him to draft something? - Tom will write it.
-他不在這里  -那把他找來
- He's not here. - Then get him here.
你劃掉的最后一段是什么
What about the last part that you crossed out?
"哀悼不是恐懼  悲痛不是認輸"
Uh, "To mourn is not to fear. To grieve is not to admit defeat."
這段應該保留
You should keep that in.
但那是假定他會死
But it presumes he's going to die.
他就是會死
He is going to die.
我們先和律師談  然后你再和媒體談
We talk to the lawyers first, then you can talk to the press.
今天已有幾個大金主退出了
I've got major funders pulling out already.
總統應該打電話安撫他們
The President should put in calls to set them at ease.
不  不打電話  競選事宜暫緩
No. No calls. The campaign's on hold.
那些資金丟了就丟了
We lose that money, so be it.
我們要穩住
We need to stabilize.
我覺得他該去掉哀悼和悲痛那一段
I don't think he should say the part about mourning and grief.
我也覺得  但耶茨說他們想保留
I agree, but Yates said they wanted it back in.
是真的嗎
Is it true?
漢默施密特寫的那些
What Hammerschmidt wrote?
-是真的嗎  -不是
- Is it? - No.
這是你不再對我說謊之后
That's the first time you've lied to me...
第一次又對我說謊了
since you stopped lying to me.
美國同胞們  過去兩年里
My fellow Americans, over the past two years,
特別是過去的幾天  幾小時里
certainly within the last several days and hours,
我都在自問  "做總統意味著什么
I have asked myself, "What does it mean to be President?
真正的領袖是什么樣的"
What does true leadership look like?"
隨著11月臨近  你們很多人
It's a question many of you have asked yourselves
也在自問這個問題
as November approaches.
我現在坐在這間辦公室的這把椅子上
Right now, as I sit in this chair, in this office,
在這里  我那么多前輩們
where so many of my predecessors
曾帶領我們國家走過動蕩
have steered our nation through turbulent times...
我發現這份工作
I realize that this job
是在政治游戲和華麗言辭之上的
is one that transcends politics and rhetoric.
坐在這個位置的人  肩負著的
Entrusted to anyone who sits behind this desk
是更為基本的東西  我們民族的生存
is something far more elemental, the very survival of our nation.
而我作為你們的總統  必須直面眼前的風暴
And I, as your President, must confront the storm before us.
這風暴便是恐怖主義
That storm is terror.
它比任何颶風都更加危險  不可預知
More dangerous and unpredictable than any hurricane.
它在國外威脅著我們
It has endangered us abroad.
在國內也威脅著我們
It has endangered us at home.
而現在  它讓詹姆斯·米勒
And right now, it has placed James Miller
處于最危險的境地中
in the gravest of dangers.
我們曾嘗試與劫持者溝通
We attempted to communicate with his captors.
我們本希望爭取一個和平的解決方案
We hoped for a peaceful solution.
我們慶幸
We're relieved that
卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒現在平安無事
Caroline and Melissa Miller are safe and sound.
但恐怖分子是蠻不講理的
But terror is blind to reason.
在放棄恐怖的機會面前
Given the opportunity to renounce terror,
尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪選擇了鼓勵恐怖
Yusuf Al Ahmadi chose to encourage it.
所以  很不幸
So, unfortunately,
我們現在要放棄講理了
we must now move beyond reason.
我們必須以武力回應
We must respond with force.
因為我們無論如何也不會釋放他
Because there is no scenario in which we will release him.
他會繼續被美國羈押  直至死亡
He will remain in United States custody until his dying breath.
如果劫持者再次來電  我們不會回答
If the captors call again, we will not answer.
溝通的階段已過  不論后果如何
The time for conversation is over, no matter the consequences.
不論詹姆斯·米勒最終是否被釋放
Regardless of whether James Miller is released or not,
是否獲救
rescued or not,
是否被殺
killed or not...
哈里發國都會被徹底摧毀
ICO will be destroyed.
我們開戰了
We are at war.
這場戰爭將比我們此前發動過的
It will be a war more total than anything we have waged thus far
任何一場反恐戰爭都更徹底
in the fight against extremism.
戰士會犧牲
Soldiers will die.
平民會傷亡
Civilians may die.
我們會承受痛苦  我們會遇到磨難
There will be pain. There will be suffering.
我們會面對人性中最可怕的一面
We will be confronted with the most horrific aspects of humanity.
我們會面對人性的喪失
We will confront the inhuman.
乃至邪惡本身
Evil itself.
但我們一定會取得勝利
But we will triumph.
這場戰爭  我們不會輸
It is not a war we will lose.
如果詹姆斯·米勒慘遭不幸
And if the worst happens to James Miller...
我們必須記住
we must remember,
哀悼不是恐懼
to mourn is not to fear,
悲痛不是認輸
to grieve is not to admit defeat.
上帝保佑美國
God bless America,
保佑所有熱愛自由和民主的人們
and all of those who believe in freedom and democracy.
-有消息嗎  -他們剛發了推特
- Any news? -They just posted on Twitter.
九點整  全網直播
9:00 sharp, live on the Internet.
我們來不及找到他們
We won't find them before that.
我們能屏蔽他們的視頻嗎
Do we have the capability to block the video?
我們能屏蔽幾個網站
Well, we might be able to block some sites,
-但如果他們的鏡像足夠多  -不用屏蔽
- but if they have enough mirrors-- - Don't block anything.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
讓全世界好好看看
The whole world should watch this.
我們也要看
And we should, too.
-你說"我們開戰了"  -我想建立個聯盟
- What you said, "We're at war..." - I want to build a coalition.
-更多空襲嗎  -地面進攻  空襲
- More air strikes? - Ground, air...
我要全軍出動
The full force of our military.
你應該先討論一下的
Well, I wish you would have consulted first.
這么大規模的升級行動
This type of escalation--
這不是升級  凱茜  是全面鏟除
Not escalation, Cathy. Obliteration.
你是想以此回應那篇報道嗎
This is your response to the article?
該做的就得做
We're doing what's necessary.
找到綁匪之后  就地正法
When you find them... you will kill them.
如果能活捉的話  我們也許能問出...
If we're able to apprehend alive, we may get--
我明白了  總統先生
I understand, Mr. President.
先生
Sir?
我想全身心投入  我能做到
I wanna be 100%. I can give you that.
但是會很不容易  因為我...
But it's gonna be a lot harder if I...
如果您需要我留在您身邊  我會的
If you want me here by your side, I will be.
-但我更想...  -不
- But I'd prefer-- - No.
需要做什么就去做  完事了再回來
You do what you have to do. Be back when it's over.
我會的  謝謝  先生
I will. Thank you, sir.
你要不要進屋去
Do you want to come inside?
-孩子們在嗎  -在
- The kids there? - Yeah.
-你不打算讓他們看...  -不
- You're not letting them watch... - No.
我禁止他們看
No, I forbade them to.
不過他們還得上學  還有朋友
Although, I mean, with school and... and their friends,
如果他們真的想看
it'll be impossible to prevent if...
我也是攔不住的
if they really wanna see it.
他們還好嗎
They all right?
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
我會好的
I will be.
我必須得好
I have to be.
這一家家的人
All these people in their houses...
馬上就要看到可怕的畫面
about to see this awful thing...
然后這輩子都忘不掉
that they'll never be able to erase.
你丈夫去世的時候  你在嗎
Were you there, when your husband died?
你在房間里嗎
In the room?
不在
No.
你曾親眼看著人死去過嗎
Have you ever watched someone die?
我知道你今晚必須得回去
I know you gotta go back there tonight...
但是等你忙完
but when you're done...
不管忙到多晚
whenever that is...
都要來這里
you're staying here.
以哈里發國和尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪的名義
We do this in the name of the Islamic Caliphate,
以真主的名義  我們處決此人
in the name of Yusuf Al Ahmadi, in the name of God.
梅莉沙  我愛你  卡洛琳  我愛你
Melissa, I love you. Caroline, I love you.
上帝啊  請照顧...
Please, dear God, look out--
把聲音關上
Turn off the sound.
沒錯
That's right.
我們不向恐怖低頭
We don't submit to terror.
我們制造恐怖
We make the terror.
■
在是否派遣地面部隊打擊伊斯蘭國的問題上  本屆美國政府一直猶豫不決
在2008年的總統大選中  奧巴馬一直批評小布什政府濫用武力
他的反戰立場  對他力壓希拉里獲得黨內提名有莫大幫助
所以奧巴馬就任后  力主從中東戰場撤兵
希望盡快結束伊拉克和阿富汗的戰事
然而樹欲靜而風不止  中東動亂不休
伊斯蘭國的崛起不僅加劇了地區性沖突
甚至直接威脅到了美國本土的國家安全
2013年阿薩德在敘利亞內戰中  多次越過奧巴馬禁用化武的"紅線"
白宮準備實施空中打擊  萬事俱備  卻在最后時刻偃旗息鼓
一些媒體認為這為后來伊斯蘭國的發展壯大提供了機會
■
由于伊拉克和阿富汗戰爭耗時過久  美國民眾普遍厭戰
但在伊斯蘭國公開處決了美國人質后  美國國內支持動武的呼聲漸高
但奧巴馬對派遣地面部隊仍有保留
2015年12月的加州恐怖襲擊案后  美軍加大了對伊斯蘭國的打擊力度
一些特種部隊士兵被派往前方執行特殊任務  但仍未大規模派遣地面部隊
在正在進行的總統選舉中  在國家安全問題上持強硬立場的幾位共和黨候選人
都在批評奧巴馬政府的中東政策
尤其是在打擊伊斯蘭國上雷聲大雨點小  目前的策略沒有成效
但幾乎所有候選人都不愿意公開支持派遣地面部隊對伊斯蘭國進行打擊
無論2016年總統選舉結果如何  奧巴馬離開白宮后
新總統面臨的最緊要的議題之一  就是如何調整中東戰場策略
決定是否要出動地面部隊對伊斯蘭國進行打擊